Guide to the Capitol Hill Restoration Society records, 1904-2012 MS2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Historic District Committee, 1973-2012; MS2009 Series 7; 2.5 Linear feet
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: A St., undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: C St., undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: Carrol St., undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: E St., undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: East Capitol St., undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: G St., undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: Independence Ave., undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: Kentucky Ave., undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: New Jersey Ave., undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: North Carolina Ave., undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: South Carolina Ave., undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: Pennsylvania Ave., undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Property surveys: South East Lettered Streets: Squares, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Property surveys: South East Numbered Streets: 2nd St., undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Property surveys: South East Numbered Streets: 3rd St., undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Property surveys: South East Numbered Streets: 4th St., undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Property surveys: South East Numbered Streets: 5th St., undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Property surveys: South East Numbered Streets: 6th St., undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Property surveys: South East Numbered Streets: 8th St., undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Property surveys: South East Numbered Streets: 9th St., undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Property surveys: South East Numbered Streets: 10th St., undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Property surveys: South East Numbered Streets: 11th St., undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Property surveys: South East Numbered Streets: 15th St., undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials, 1986-1993 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Architectural Details, undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Christ Church, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Christ Church, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Committee Notes, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Eastern Market, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Eastern Market, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Eastern Market, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Eastern Market, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Eastern Market, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Eastern Market clippings, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Eastern Market, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Eastern Market, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Ellen Wilson Dwelling monitoring, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Flyers, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Grant, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Guide, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Guide, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Historic Preservation Review Board, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Library of Congress, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Pennsylvania 1200 Block, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Prosper Court / Sousa Neighborhood Association, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Prosper Court / Sousa Neighborhood Association, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Schauer Historic District Committee materials: Signage, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Information - interiors, 1988 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - H.D. survey - Lally/Overbeck grant proposal, 1995 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - DC historic preservation plan, 1996 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Ellen Wilson, 1996 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Fagon guide, 1996 September 10 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Historic District, 1996 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Historic district articles, 1996 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - HD cases-1996 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - 321 Mass. Ave, N.E., 1996-1997 (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - Signs, 1996-1997 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - HPRB cases, 1997 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Peabody School, 1997 (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - Historic District Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 168, Folder 13)
  - 1998 (Box 168, Folder 14)
  - Enforcement, 1998 (Box 168, Folder 15)
  - HPRB cases, 1998 January - 1998 May (Box 168, Folder 16)
  - June 1998 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - July 1998 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - August 1998 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - September 1998 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - October 1998 [1/2] (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - October 1998 [2/2] (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - November 1998 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - February 1999 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - March 1999 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - April 1999 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - May 1999 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - June 1999 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - July 1999 (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - August 1999 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - September 1999 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - October 1999 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - November 1999 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - December 1999 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - H. St. Information 721-727 H St. NE, 1999 July - September (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Design guidelines-general history, 1987-1992 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Historic districts-general, 1988-1998 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Infill structures, 1990-1997 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Public space, 1994-1997 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Carriage House, 1996-1998 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - HD Com, 1997 (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - January 2000 (Box 170, Folder 13)
  - February 2000 (Box 170, Folder 14)
  - Atlas Theatre landmark, 2000 March (Box 170, Folder 15)
  - March 2000 (Box 170, Folder 16)
  - April 2000 (Box 170, Folder 17)
  - May 2000 (Box 170, Folder 18)
  - June 2000 [1/2] (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - June 2000 [2/2] (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - July 2000 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - October 2000 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - September 2000 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - November 2000 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - December 2000 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - January 2001 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - February 2001 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - March 2001 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - April 2001 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - May 2001 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - June 2001 [1/2] (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - June 2001 [2/2] (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - July 2001 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - August 2001 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - September 2001 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - October 2001 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - November 2001 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - November 2001 [1/2] (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - November 2001 [2/2] (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - December 2001 [1/2] (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - December 2001 [2/2] (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - January 2002 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - February 2002 [1/2] (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - February 2002 [2/2] (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - March 2002 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - April 2002 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - May 2002 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - June 2002 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - 315 East Capitol St., 2002 May - June (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Results pool fall, 2002 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - May 2003 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - June 2003 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - July 2003 (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - September 2003 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - November 2003 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - April-October 2003, 2003 April - October (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - January 2004 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - February 2004 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - March 2004 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - April 2004 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - May 2004 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - June 2004 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - July 2004 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - September 2004 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - October 2004 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - November 2004 (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - December 2004 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - HPRB case summaries, 2004-2008 (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - January 2005 (Box 176, Folder 13)
  - February 2005 (Box 176, Folder 14)
  - March 2005 (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - April 2005 HPRB (Box 176, Folder 16)
  - May 2005 HPRB [1/2] (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - May 2005 HPRB [2/2] (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - June 2005 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - July 2005 [1/2] (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - July 2005 [2/2] (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - September 2005 [1/2] (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - September 2005 [2/2] (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - October 2005 [1/2] (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - October 2005 [2/2] (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - November 2005 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - December 2005 (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - 2005-2006 [1/3] (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - 2005-2006 [2/3] (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - 2005-2006 [3/3] (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - January 2006 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - February 2006 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - March 2006 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - April 2006 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - May 2006 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - June 2006 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - July 2006 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - September 2006 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - October 2006 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - November 2006 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - December 2006 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - January 2007 [1/2] (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - January 2007 [2/2] (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - February 2007 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - March 2007 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - April 2007 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - May 2007 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - June 2007 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - July 2007 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - September 2007 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - October 2007 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - November 2007 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - December 2007 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - January 2008 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - February 2008 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - March 2008 [1/2] (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - March 2008 [2/2] (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - April 2008 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - May 2008 [1/2] (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - May 2008 [2/2] (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - June 2008 [1/2] (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - June 2008 [2/2] (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - July 2008 [1/4] (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - July 2008 [2/4] (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - July 2008 [3/4], 2008 July (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - July 2008 [4/4] (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - September 2008 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - October 2008 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - November 2008 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - December 2008 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - January 2009 [1/2] (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - January 2009 [2/2] (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - February 2009 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - March 2009 [1/2] (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - March 2009 [2/2] (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - April 2009 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - May 2009 [1/2] (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - May 2009 [2/2] (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - June 2009 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - July 2009 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - September 2009 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - October 2009 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - November 2009 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - December 2009 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - December 2009-2010, 2009 December - 2010 December (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - January 2010 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - February 2010 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - March 2010 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - April 2010 [1/2] (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - April 2010 [2/2] (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - May 2010 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - June 2010 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - July 2010 [1/2] (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - July 2010 [2/2] (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - September 2010 [1/3] (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - September 2010 [2/3] (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - September 2010 [3/3] (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - October 2010 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - November 2010 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - December 2010 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - January 2011 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - February 2011 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - March 2011 [1/2] (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - March 2011 [2/2] (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - April 2011 [1/2] (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - April 2011 [2/2] (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - May 2011 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - June 2011 [1/2] (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - June 2011 [2/2] (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - June 2011 HINE (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - July 2011 [1/2] (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - July 2011 [2/2] (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - September 2011 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - October 2011 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - November 2011 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - December 2011 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - HINE April - July, 2011 (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - HINE School, 2012 (Box 192, Folder 10)
- Historical files, 1949-1989; MS2009 Series 8; 2 Linear feet
  This series contains articles of incorporation, by-laws, booklets, legislative bills, reports, articles and writings, a scrapbook, newspaper clippings, newsletters, and informational brochures. This material covers the years 1949-94. This series serves as a catch all for materials that relate to different aspects of CHRS. Some of the files deal with the history of the organization such as those related to the Society's archives, while other materials relate to work the CHRS did for a particular project such as the government expansion of the Hine School. This series appears to have been created to serve as a repository for materials that did not otherwise have a home in the collection. Topics include black history, expansion projects, freeways, the metro, memorials and public art, neighborhood amenity, planning, architecture and urbanization; real estate, social change, local policies, and zoning.
  - History: Administration Procedures D.C., undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - History: Aerial Views of Capitol Hill, 1949-1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - History: Archives for the Society: Donations, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - History: Archives for the Society: Loans, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - History: Archives for the Society: Oral History, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - History: Archives for the Society: Policy, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - History: Archives for the Society: Society Structure and Officers, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - History: Archives for the Society: Survey, D.C. Archival Project, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - History: Archives for the Society: Trivia, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - History: Articles, 1958-1996 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - History: Articles of Incorporation and Bylaws, 1974-1980 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - History: Brief History of the CHRS and its Objectives, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - History: Booklet, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - History: Capitol Hill School, 1956-1975 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - History: Challenge--Transforming Capitol Hill October, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - History: Communities reaction to the CHRS's activities -- survey findings, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - History: Congressional Cemetery, 1937-1974 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - History: Construction of 330 Housing Units on Square 1020 November 5, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - History: Correspondence, general, 1975-1989 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - History: Correspondence about Historic Houses Documentation Mrs. Govan, 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - History: Department of Housing and Community Development: Notices of Final Rulemaking, undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - History: D.C. Downtown Historic Area, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - History: D.C. Government--Advisory Neighborhood Councils, undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - History: D.C. Government--D.C. Council member, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - History: D.C. Government--Home Rule, undated (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - History: D.C. Government--Permit Parking, undated (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - History: D.C. Government--Positions before Council, undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - History: Friendship House, undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - History: Government Expansion Attempts--Capitol Expansion miscellaneous cares and plans, undated (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - History: Government Expansion Attempts--Capitol Underground Garages, undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - History: Government Expansion Attempts--East Mall proposal, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - History: Government Expansion Attempts--Hines School, undated (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - History: Government Expansion Attempts--Library of Congress extension 1st Mark's site, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - History: Government Expansion Attempts--Library of Congress extension Parking and St. Mark's site, 1963-1965 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - History: Government Expansion Attempts--Library of Congress Extension, 1960-1962 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - History: Government Expansion Attempts--Master Plan, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - History: Government Expansion Attempts--Maryland Ave. N.E. and 3rd Square 757, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - History: Historic District, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - History: Historic District Nominations, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - History: House Tour Scrapbook, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - History: House Tours, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - History: Landmarks of the National Capital Designated by the Joint Committee of Landmarks of the National Capital, 1983 June 30 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - History: L'Enfant's Methods, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - History: Mayor's Downtown Committee, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - History: Miscellaneous documents, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - History: Miscellaneous Pictures and Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - History: Navy Yard--Newspaper Clippings, 1949-1964 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - History: Only a Few of the Many Fine Historic Places and People on Old Capitol Hill, SE, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - History: Personalities on Capitol Hill--Boswell, Haller, Burklin, Green, 1962-1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - History: Places and Persons on Capitol Hill, Stories and Pictures of a Neighborhood, 1960 May (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - History: Planning for Area--Bills to make Capitol Hill National Historic Area, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - History: Planning for Area--Halprin Report, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - History: Planning for Area--Kennedy Center Location and Use, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - History: Planning for Area--Plan & Revision as Comprehension Plan, 1965-1967 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - History: Planning for Area--New Jersey Avenue, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - History: Rehabilitation Standards for Historic Buildings of the D.C. Department of Recreation., undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - History: Ward VI Profile, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - History: Washington-the Design of the Federal City, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - History: Washington From Banneker to Douglass, 1791-1870 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - History: Washington In the New Era, 1870-1970 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - History: Welcome to the Nation's Capital brochure, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - History: Yale University -- Private Urban Renewal project, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Road and transit takeovers: Inner Loop, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Road and transit takeovers: Inner Loop, 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Road and transit takeovers: Metro, 1966-1975 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Road and transit takeovers: Southeast Freeway, 1970-1973 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Restoration: Alley Dwelling Restoration, 1949-1960 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Restoration: Apartments on Capitol Hill -- Restoration, 1953-1964 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Restoration: Belmont House, 1955-1959 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Restoration: John Phillip Sousa's House, 1962-1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Restoration: Museum of African Art in the Fredrick Douglass House, 1964-1969 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Restoration: Washington Preservation Conference, 1972 April 14 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Older structures -- preservation and use: BB French School, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Older structures -- preservation and use: Car Barn, 1966-1968 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Older structures -- preservation and use: Florida House, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Older structures -- preservation and use: Half-way Houses, 1962-1972 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Older structures -- preservation and use: Marine Corps Barracks extension, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Older structures -- preservation and use: Union Station -- Visitors Center, 1964-1975 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - 1961 articles, 1961 May - September; MS2009 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - 1964 articles, 1964 Novemeber 27; MS2009 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - 1967 articles, books, brochures, MS2009 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Black history, 1961, 1969 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - CHRS newsletters + Barbara Held (realtor) newsletters, 1961-1972 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - CHRS + related in local news 60-70, 1960-1968 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - East Mall Capitol expansion, etc., 1960-1970 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Home Rule & local policies, 1961-1971 (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Freeways, 1960-1972 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Metro, 1959-1970 (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Misc. & duplicate material [1/2], 1960-1994 (Box 193, Folder 12)
  - Misc. & duplicate material [2/2], 1960-1994 (Box 193, Folder 13)
  - Neighborhood amenity, 1960-1970 (Box 193, Folder 14)
  - Planning, architecture & urbanization, 1960-1970 (Box 193, Folder 15)
  - Real estate & misc., 1959-1970 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Restoration misc., 1960-1971 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Social change + local politics, 1967-1970 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Undated clippings, books, etc., 1959-1994 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Union Station restoration/Visitor Center, 1967-1972 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Zoning, 1961-1971 (Box 194, Folder 6)
- Leukhardt family papers, 1900-1995; MS2009 Series 9; 0.5 Linear feet
  This series contains newspaper articles, correspondence, an oral history, photographs, telephone directory, programs, by-laws, and minutes. This material covers the years 1900-95. The series has material related to the Capitol Hill neighborhood including a good early history of several prominent residents in 'Only a Few of the Many Fine Historic Places and People on Old Capitol Hill, Southeast" written in 1953 by Elizabeth Draper and the records from the Southeast Citizens' Association and the Washington Housing Authority. There is a program for the National Capital Centennial from 1900 and material about the Old Marine Hospital. The series does not have much material about the Yost or Leukhardt families, but does have historical material about the Capitol Hill neighborhood and about the purchase of the Yost House by the CHRS.
  William Henry Yost built his house at 1002 Pennsylvania Ave. in 1894. The house passed to his daughter Elsie and she lived there with her husband John C. Leukhardt until they sold the house to the Capitol Hill Restoration Society in 1979. The Yost House became the headquarters for CHRS.
  - Crime: Combating Crime in the United States, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Crime: Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Crime: Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Family papers: Correspondence, 1969-1979 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Family papers: General file, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Family papers: J. C. Leukhardt Papers, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Family papers: Oral History Mrs. Leukhardt, undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Family papers: Photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Family papers: Photographs--Negatives for the Washington Post Story, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Family papers: Photographs--Thanksgiving, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Family papers: Washington Post Article about the Thanksgiving, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Family papers: Photographs and Negatives, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)